<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Drew's Private Feed: Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project]]></title><description><![CDATA[Drew's Private Feed: Andy Daly (Comedy Central's Review) and Matt Gourley (Superego) spent months sifting through podcast pilots to curate this collection of noteworthy efforts. Together they’ll bring you pilots submitted by a beloved cowboy poet, a satanist game show host and many more. All of these would-be podcasters have, oddly enough, taken advantage of the open door policy on Comedy Bang Bang, but there is so much more to discover about each and every one of them.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.

This feed was generated by Drew for private use.]]></description><link>https://www.stitcher.com/show/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project</link><image><url>https://stitcher.imgix.net/0fa8bbd175a9ea6bc812ef8b4f2229c4ed118e3831b97a3c15c7784022f229f5?w=600&amp;h=600&amp;q=75</url><title>Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project</title><link>https://www.stitcher.com/show/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project</link></image><generator>Unofficial RSS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:20:55 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drews-little-helpers.herokuapp.com/feeds/1001557.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 01:20:55 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[Andy Daly Podcast Project]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><ttl>60</ttl><itunes:author>Andy Daly Podcast Project</itunes:author><itunes:summary>This podcast is not a Stitcher premium feed. Some episodes may not be added to the feed. You may want to subscribe to this podcast&apos;s public feed.

Andy Daly (Comedy Central&apos;s Review) and Matt Gourley (Superego) spent months sifting through podcast pilots to curate this collection of noteworthy efforts. Together they’ll bring you pilots submitted by a beloved cowboy poet, a satanist game show host and many more. All of these would-be podcasters have, oddly enough, taken advantage of the open door policy on Comedy Bang Bang, but there is so much more to discover about each and every one of them.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.

This feed was generated at UnofficialRSS.com for private use.</itunes:summary><itunes:block>yes</itunes:block><googleplay:block>yes</googleplay:block><itunes:owner><itunes:name>Unofficial RSS</itunes:name><itunes:email>help@unofficialrss.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="https://stitcher.imgix.net/0fa8bbd175a9ea6bc812ef8b4f2229c4ed118e3831b97a3c15c7784022f229f5?w=600&amp;h=600&amp;q=75"/><item><title><![CDATA[Re-Release: The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project Season 1, Episode 1: “The Wit and Wisdom of The West with Dalton Wilcox”]]></title><description><![CDATA[This episode is a free episode. This podcast feed may no longer be a premium feed.

SUBSCRIBE TO THE ANDY DALY PODCAST PROJECT AT:  patreon.com/AndyDaly Dalton Wilcox, cowboy poet and author of “You Must Buy Your Wife At Least As Much Jewelry As You Buy Your Horse and Other Poems and Observations, Humorous and Otherwise, From a Life on The Range,” throws his hat into the podcast ring with this rustic perspective on life and poetry on the range. Dalton’s guests include his publisher, Rustle Shine, fellow cowboy poets Sally Jespa and Bartleby Mulcahy, and a live performance by world renowned country/western band, The Journeymen.  Featuring: Matt Gourley, Paul F. Tompkins, Betsy Sodaro, Sean Conroy, Jeremy Carter, Mark McConville, and James Bladon. Announcer: Billy Merritt “ADPPP Theme Music” by Dave Wilder, wilderstylemusic.com  Merch: redbubble.com/people/ADPodProject/shop  Mail: PO Box 9407 Glendale, CA 91226  Andy’s website: andydaly.com   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://patreon.com/AndyDaly</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-300088879</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2023 07:17:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://sphinx.acast.com/p/open/s/6411e8161cc77a0010074ae1/e/d769ebeb-1622-456c-a51f-afb3014fb993/media.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>1</itunes:season><itunes:duration>7458</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Out now: Bonanas For Bonanza, the series!]]></title><description><![CDATA[This episode is a free episode. This podcast feed may no longer be a premium feed.

Dalton Wilcox announces the return of Bonanas for Bonanza, now picked up by Earwolf for a full season! Subscribe now&nbsp;and listen to the first episode on Stitcher, Apple Podcasts, or wherever&nbsp;you get your podcasts.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/out-now-bonanas-for-bonanza-the-series</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196576</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2020 19:46:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/aaea4e69-af51-495e-afc9-a9760146922b/2f221518-53f6-4aaa-b3eb-aa86015d7469/987445af-0a6c-46e4-81f5-abac0145bc48/audio.mp3?utm_source=Podcast&amp;in_playlist=fa6139ac-7f87-4d72-98e1-aa86015d7477" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>55</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Season 2 Teaser Trailer]]></title><description><![CDATA[This episode is a free episode. This podcast feed may no longer be a premium feed.

Matt and Andy are back with Season 2 of the Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project coming to you for FREE&nbsp;September 6th! Get your eardrums ready for a lil' taste with this teaser trailer.&nbsp; Check out The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project Apple Podcasts:&nbsp;https://itunes.apple.com/us/podcast/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/id774375605?mt=2&amp;at=1l3va5V&amp;ct=wp&nbsp; Stitcher: https://bit.ly/StitcherADPPP]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/season-2-teaser-trailer</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196585</guid><pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2018 20:57:12 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/aaea4e69-af51-495e-afc9-a9760146922b/2f221518-53f6-4aaa-b3eb-aa86015d7469/1a26a847-5959-439e-a3cf-aa86015e3614/audio.mp3?utm_source=Podcast&amp;in_playlist=fa6139ac-7f87-4d72-98e1-aa86015d7477" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>trailer</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>293</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Travel Bug Live! with August Lindt]]></title><description><![CDATA[Andy and Matt are giving ol’ August Lindt another shot with Travel Bug recorded live at The Largo in Los Angeles.&nbsp;August is joined by other famous travel bugs, Werner Herzog, Pope Benedict XIII, and H.R. Giger to discuss their favorite travels.&nbsp;Then the whole Lindt family pop's by to update us on what they've been up to since we last heard from them four years.&nbsp;And to close out the evening German super-group, Spyryt performs their hits. Special Guests: Matt Besser, Paul F. Tompkins, Jeremy Carter, James Bladon, Chris Tallman, Mark McConville, Erinn Hayes, Todd Cooper, and Tony Thaxton   This episode is brought to you by Heineken and Casper Mattresses (www.casper.com/andydaly code: ANDYDALY).]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/8-the-travel-bug-live-with-august-lindt</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196577</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196577.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>5724</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Long Story with Alexandra Higgs Portman]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last summer, a man who goes by the name of Cactus Tony was arrested for murder. But a letter from his employer sent to The Pasadena News Press Times Gazette claims he is innocent, leading journalist Alexandra Higgs Portman down a dark path to the truth. The deeper she digs, the stranger it gets. From The Pasadena News Press Times Gazette and Earwolf Media, this is The Long Story Podcast.&nbsp;  Special Guests: Amanda Lund, Sean Conroy, Carl Tart, Jeremy Carter, Betsy Sodaro, Maria Blasucci   This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/7-the-long-story-with-alexandra-higgs-portman</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196578</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196578.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>5109</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ship to Shore with L. Ron Hubbard]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recorded live, November 10th, 1968 aboard the Sea Org Flagship, The Royal Scotsman, this is Ship To Shore with “The Commodore,” L. Ron Hubbard.&nbsp;LRH is joined by some of his most trusted advisors like Marion Grapes, Heidi Corporate and Jules McManon, for important updates about the goings on in the church.&nbsp;We learn about everyone’s past lives, and how a treasure hunt through time has been going.&nbsp;Then, they all play a rousing game of “Stump The Clear”, and Martin Margotdale, skeptic and magician, tires to debate The Commodore.&nbsp;Finally, the group puts on a radio play of one of L. Ron’s greatest works. NOTE: This pilot is not for suppressive persons!  Special Guests: Lauren Lapkus, Mary Holland, Matt Gourley and Paul F. Tompkins  This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/6-ship-to-shore-with-l-ron-hubbard</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196579</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196579.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>5937</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Gil & Golly Variety Hour]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recorded LIVE from the Day Room of the Towering Pines Psychiatric Hospital and Long Term Care Facility, it’s The Gil &amp; Golly Variety Hour! Your host's Gil and his pal Golly, welcome classic vaudeville act Milton &amp; Dupree, who are, well, older than they used to be.&nbsp;David Bowie drops by, along with Rufus Goodfoot the original blind musician.&nbsp;Followed by the adorable tap dancing Celinda Dimples, and more!&nbsp;All these acts are true talents and definitely NOT insane!&nbsp;  Special guests: Jeremy Carter, Matt Gourley, Matt Besser, Carl Tart, Jessica McKenna, and Scott Aukerman   This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/5-the-gil-golly-variety-hour</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196580</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196580.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>4231</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Terrifying Edinburgh with Cameron MacGonagle]]></title><description><![CDATA[Beware, this week’s pilot is very, very scary! Join Cameron MacGonagle for a terrifying tour of Edinburgh's spookiest establishments and meet the quirky spirits that haunt their halls. From a very thirsty ghost, to a long dead board playing cannibal, and a truly other worldly being! Proceed with caution because this podcast will&nbsp;chill you straight down to the bone.&nbsp;Guest Starring: Jessica Chaffin, Lauren Lapkus, Sean Conroy, Paul F. Tompkins, Matt Gourley and Mary Holland.&nbsp; This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/4-terrifying-edinburgh-with-cameron-macgonagle</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196581</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Mar 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196581.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>4995</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Pee Tape with Don DiMello]]></title><description><![CDATA[Theatrical director, Don DiMello is back, this time with a political podcast pilot devoted entirely to the infamous Pee Tape.&nbsp;Don is joined by co-host Falcon, keeper of the retired Rockettes farm.&nbsp;Theatre critic Mal Bachman stops by, along with surveillance expert, Bob Fredricks, who teaches the gang how to strategically hide cameras and compose the perfect blackmail letter.&nbsp;Finally, Irina Gotsikova explains the art of a custom Pee Tape.&nbsp;  Special Guests: Jason Mantzoukas, Matt Gourley, Eddie Pepitone, and Mary Birdsong   This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/3-the-pee-tape-with-don-dimello</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196582</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Mar 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196582.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>4560</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Drivin' and F***kin' with Joe Bongo and Margot Chunk]]></title><description><![CDATA[Joe Bongo, Marina Del Rey's very own Sex Ed Teacher and drug survivor, is joined by his friend and replacement Drivers Ed Instructor Margot Chunk to answer your questions on Sex and Driving. They are joined by Marissa Wompler and her mentor Charlotte "Char-dog" Listler who help Joe and Margot explore more questions about the mysteries of reproduction. Finally, Joe wraps up this pilot with a few songs from his prod-rock band, Rosebush Red.&nbsp;  Special guests: Betsy Sodaro, Lennon Parham, Jessica St. Clair, Mark McConville, Daniel Michicoff, and James Bladon.&nbsp;  This episode is brought to you by Heineken and Casper Mattresses (www.casper.com/andydaly).]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/2-drivin-and-f-kin-with-joe-bongo-and-margot-chunk</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196583</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196583.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>5904</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bonanas for Bonanza with Dalton Wilcox]]></title><description><![CDATA[Cowboy Poet Laureate of the West, Dalton Wilcox is back to try his hand at another podcast pilot. This time, he is doing his own re-watch podcast of the classic tv show, Bonanza! On this episode Dalton is joined by his old old old friend, Bartleby Mokay, as well as his reluctant city slickin' book publisher, Russell Shine to discuss the pilot of Bonanza! Later, they welcome The Journeymen to hear tell of their adventure in making the Bonanza sequel, Moonanza!&nbsp; Special guests: Sean Conroy, Paul F. Tompkins, Jeremy Carter, Mark McConville, Tony Thaxton, Daniel Michicoff, and James Bladon  You can binge listen to the entire season now on Stitcher Premium. For a free month of Premium, go to&nbsp;stitcherpremium.com/andy&nbsp;and use promo code 'ANDY'.    This episode is brought to you by Heineken.]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/1-bonanas-for-bonanza-with-dalton-wilcox</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196584</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Mar 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196584.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>6491</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Season 2 Teaser Episode]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project Season 2 teaser episode with Matt Gourley and Andy Daly. Special guest/podcast King Scott Aukerman joins Andy &amp; Matt to discuss why the previous pilots from Season 1 were not picked up and the new submitted podcast pilots whose hosts have oddly enough taken advantage of the open door policy on Comedy Bang! Bang! Listen to Season 2 starting Thursday, March 8th on Stitcher Premium! For a free month trial, go to stitcherpremium.com/andy and use promo code ‘ANDY’.    This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: ANDY).]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/the-season-2-teaser-episode</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196586</guid><pubDate>Thu, 01 Mar 2018 08:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196586.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>bonus</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>2</itunes:season><itunes:duration>2789</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kiss Me, I'm Patrick McMahon LIVE!]]></title><description><![CDATA[The time has come for the season finale of The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project as Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley present a star-studded event hosted by Irish Storyteller Patrick McMahon LIVE from Molly Malones Irish Pub in Los Angeles! Tune in as Patrick shares some of his famous Irish tales, Monsignor Damien Fearnly blesses the podcast &amp; performs petite miracles, Lucian Charms aka the President of the Ancient Order of Hibernians bestows a great honor to a special Irishman, and The Irishmen play some traditional Irish music. Plus, Patricks brother Sheamus McMahon makes an appearance to challenge everyone to a limerick off for the title of Irish Person of the Year. Special thanks to Daniel Michicoff and Jesse Olema for their phenomenal bass &amp; fiddle playing and fan Jeremy Asher Fried - tealeafonthewind.com&nbsp;- for the wonderful pictures of the evening. Remember to tune into Review on Comedy Central, Thursdays at 10pm! This episode is sponsored by: Squarespace: Use offer code ANDY for a free trial. Bonobos: Use offer code ANDY for a 20% discount off your first purchase of better fitting mens clothes. NatureBox: Go to naturebox.com/andy for 50% off your first box of delicious snacks.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196588</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Mar 2014 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196588.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5768</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rockin' and A Rollin' with Wolfman Hot Dog]]></title><description><![CDATA[Get excited as Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley present a love letter to waterskiing &amp; Rock 'n' Roll's Sha Na Na hosted by Wolfman Hot Dog. Join aspiring Sha Na Na member Wolfman Hot Dog as he shares a portion of his Dreams and Aspirations journal, chats with waterskiing legend Ahi &amp; his cousin Penny about the golden age of waterskiing, and asks former Sha Na Na member Slammin Oliver Rothwell about his time in the band. Plus, the biggest Sha Na Na fan Veronica Melcher drops by for some Sha Na Na Trivia.Dont forget to tune into Review on Comedy Central, Thursdays at 10pm! This episode is sponsored by: Bonobos : Use offer code ANDY for a 20% discount off your first purchase of better fitting men's clothes.NatureBox: Go to naturebox.com/andy for 50% off your first box of delicious snacks.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196589</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Mar 2014 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196589.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5792</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Shut Up and Have Fun with Danny Mahoney]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gather some friends because it's time to party! Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley bring you yet another interactive podcast pilot from dyed-in-the-wool New Yorker Danny Mahoney of Life of the Party Inc. Hang out with Danny &amp; his party crew Donnie, Marianna and Fireplug as they have a cocktail party filled with music, games, and a cooking segment with celerity chef Rene Dupree. But it wouldn't be a party without a good ol' fashioned game of Name That Tune with some family. Luckily, Danny's nephew Bert drops by with keyboardist Jimmy Blades just in time to join in on the festivities.Don't forget to tune into Review on Comedy Central, Thursdays at 10pm!&nbsp;This episode is sponsored by: Bonobos : Use offer code ANDY for a 20% discount off your first purchase of better fitting mens clothes. Squarespace : Use offer code ANDY for a free trial and 10%off.NatureBox: Go to naturebox.com/andy for 50% off your first box of delicious snacks.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196590</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Mar 2014 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196590.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5794</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Eye On Theatre with Don DiMello]]></title><description><![CDATA[If you're a fan of the theatre then this podcast pilot is right up your alley! This week Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley present a podcast pilot all about the theatre from the unique perspective of theatrical director Don DiMello . Along with his co-host/theatre critic Mal Bachman, they'll share a bit about their theatre background and review 3 current Los Angeles theatre productions. Then their longtime acquaintance Falcon drops by to explain what his job is when The Rockettes are no longer able to perform. Plus, Don gives aspiring star of the stage &amp; Comedy Bang! Bang! intern Marissa Wompler a few tips on becoming a star as part of his mentorship.Come see a live taping of the Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project at Molly Malone's Irish Pub in Los Angeles on TUESDAY, MARCH 11th at 8:30 pm.Go to http://store.earwolf.com/products/andy-daly-live for tickets!Also, tune in tonight (March 6th) for Review on Comedy Central at 10pm! This episode is sponsored by: Bonobos : Use offer code ANDY for a 20% discount off your first purchase of better fitting men's clothes.NatureBox: Go to naturebox.com/andy for 50% off your first box of delicious snacks.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196591</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Mar 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196591.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5944</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Travel Bug with August Lindt]]></title><description><![CDATA[You're in for a treat as Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley bring you a remarkable festival of German accents in a travel themed podcast pilot hosted by pretzel maker/world traveler August Lindt . August is in fantastic German company as he welcomes legendary director Werner Herzog, surrealist painter/sculptor H.R. Giger, and our former holiness Pope Benedict XVI to get acquainted with one another, share some travel tips, and recommend wonderful travel destinations. Plus, they play a game called Where In The World Are My Wife and Children?If you're in Los Angeles, dont miss a LIVE taping of The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project with Irish storyteller Patrick McMahon on Tuesday, March 11th at Molly Malones Irish Pub. Go to http://www.mollymalonesla.com / for more info!Also, mark your calendars as the premiere of Review on Comedy Central is on March 6th at 10pm!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196592</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196592.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5602</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Get Fit Now with Bill Carter]]></title><description><![CDATA[On today's episode, Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley have chosen a unique interactive podcast experience in a pilot hosted by 91-year-old Personal Trainer to the Stars Bill Carter . Bill will lead you through the steps needed for the workout of a lifetime, he'll chat with his good friends Victor the Giant &amp; Rochelle the Elf, former Wrestler/Governor Jesse "The Body" Ventura will make an appearance to challenge the listener, and everyone will answer some questions from Twitter about fitness. Plus, you'll be treated with the world premiere of the greatest workout song ever to be written since "Eye of the Tiger" by the one and only Spyryt.If you're in Los Angeles, dont miss a LIVE taping of The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project with Irish storyteller Patrick McMahon on Tuesday, March 11th at Molly Malones Irish Pub. Go to http://www.mollymalonesla.com / for more info!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196593</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196593.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5494</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Hail Satan with Chip Gardner]]></title><description><![CDATA[Things get grizzly as Andy Daly &amp; Matt Gourley bring us the next podcast pilot hosted by Broadcaster and Game Show Host Chip Gardner . With his trusty longtime announcer Tip Thompson, Chip &amp; Tip will recall past game show failures, play some of their favorite games from over the years, and share tips &amp; recommend chips to listeners in a segment called Chip's Tips &amp; Tip's Chips. Plus, Chip will debate formidable opponent Carol Channing for the honorary position of Mayor of Hollywood and we are taken through a day in the life of a feeble-minded man named Chocolate Pudding in Chocolate Pudding Does Whatever The Fuck He Wants.If you're in Los Angeles, dont miss a LIVE taping of The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project with Irish storyteller Patrick McMahon on Tuesday, March 11th at Molly Malones Irish Pub. Go to http://www.mollymalonesla.com / for more info!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196594</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Feb 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196594.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5536</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Wit and Wisdom of the West with Dalton Wilcox]]></title><description><![CDATA[Andy Daly and Matt Gourley kick things off with a bang as they bring us the first podcast pilot hosted by Poet Laureate of the West Dalton Wilcox. Expect a true story from Dalton's week out on the range, a chat with Rustle Shine, the city slickin' publisher of his book "You Must Buy Your Wife At Least As Much Jewelry As You Buy Your Horse and Other Poems and Observations, Humorous and Otherwise, From a Life on The Range," a Cowboy Poetry Workshop with fellow cowboy poets Sally Jespa &amp; Bartleby Mckay, and music from one of the best Country Western bands in the world, The (Goddamned) Journeymen. Make sure to head over to earwolf.com/dalton to participate in the Dalton Wilcox Book Store Challenge and grab yourself The Journeymen's album "Mount Us More" over at http://gosuperego.bandcamp.com/album/mount-us-more !If youre in Los Angeles, dont miss a LIVE taping of The Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project with Irish storyteller Patrick McMahon on Tuesday, March 11th at Molly Malones Irish Pub. Go to http://www.mollymalonesla.com / for more info!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196595</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Feb 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200196595.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>7420</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>false</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>false</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Teaser Episode]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the Andy Daly Podcast Pilot Project explainer, introduction, and teaser episode with Earwolf producer Matt Gourley (Superego) and Andy Daly (the upcoming Comedy Central series Review). Special guest/podcast King Scott Aukerman joins Andy &amp; Matt to discuss the premise of the podcast and some of the submitted podcast pilots whose hosts have oddly enough taken advantage of the open door policy on Comedy Bang! Bang!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/the-andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200230839</guid><pubDate>Mon, 16 Dec 2013 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001557/200230839.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>trailer</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2158</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Find Full Archive of Andy Daly Pilot Project on Stitcher Premium]]></title><description><![CDATA[This episode is a free episode. This podcast feed may no longer be a premium feed.

Find Full Archive of Andy Daly Pilot Project on Stitcher Premium by Andy Daly Pilot Project]]></description><link>https://omny.fm/shows/andy-daly-podcast-pilot-project/find-full-archive-of-andy-daly-pilot-project-on-st</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200196587</guid><pubDate>Fri, 01 Nov 2013 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="https://traffic.omny.fm/d/clips/aaea4e69-af51-495e-afc9-a9760146922b/2f221518-53f6-4aaa-b3eb-aa86015d7469/8398b246-b7ed-437c-aef2-aa86015ef011/audio.mp3?utm_source=Podcast&amp;in_playlist=fa6139ac-7f87-4d72-98e1-aa86015d7477" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>bonus</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>91</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item></channel></rss>