<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0" xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd" xmlns:googleplay="http://www.google.com/schemas/play-podcasts/1.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Drew's Private Feed: I Was There Too]]></title><description><![CDATA[Drew's Private Feed: If you're like Matt Gourley (Superego, Drunk History, Conan O'Brien Needs A Friend), then you know all the classic movie and television scenes so well it's like you were in the room when they happened. Well, you weren't. And neither was he. But the people Matt interviews were! Listen in as they tell the inside stories of how cinema and television history was made from a fly-on-the-wall perspective you've never heard.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.

This feed was generated by Drew for private use.]]></description><link>https://www.stitcher.com/show/i-was-there-too</link><image><url>https://stitcher.imgix.net/47c907ded268b6493d132e58b292e1ce6db911362e2dbc37529dbc1c5f6159bf?w=600&amp;h=600&amp;q=75</url><title>I Was There Too</title><link>https://www.stitcher.com/show/i-was-there-too</link></image><generator>Unofficial RSS</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:17:02 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://drews-little-helpers.herokuapp.com/feeds/1001575.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:17:02 GMT</pubDate><copyright><![CDATA[Matt Gourley]]></copyright><language><![CDATA[en]]></language><ttl>60</ttl><itunes:author>Matt Gourley</itunes:author><itunes:summary>This podcast is not a Stitcher premium feed. Some episodes may not be added to the feed. You may want to subscribe to this podcast&apos;s public feed.

If you&apos;re like Matt Gourley (Superego, Drunk History, Conan O&apos;Brien Needs A Friend), then you know all the classic movie and television scenes so well it&apos;s like you were in the room when they happened. Well, you weren&apos;t. And neither was he. But the people Matt interviews were! Listen in as they tell the inside stories of how cinema and television history was made from a fly-on-the-wall perspective you&apos;ve never heard.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.

This feed was generated at UnofficialRSS.com for private use.</itunes:summary><itunes:block>yes</itunes:block><googleplay:block>yes</googleplay:block><itunes:owner><itunes:name>Unofficial RSS</itunes:name><itunes:email>help@unofficialrss.com</itunes:email></itunes:owner><itunes:image href="https://stitcher.imgix.net/47c907ded268b6493d132e58b292e1ce6db911362e2dbc37529dbc1c5f6159bf?w=600&amp;h=600&amp;q=75"/><item><title><![CDATA[Get Rich Nick Trailer]]></title><description><![CDATA[Hey I Was There Too listeners - here is a new Earwolf show, out today!&nbsp;Nick Turner and Nick Vatterott clumsily try every get-rich-quick scheme under the sun in an attempt to profit while teaching listeners the ins and outs of each money-making endeavor. With a new scheme every week and interviews with friends/specialists, we will see if the Nicks can get rich beyond their mildest dreams.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198519</guid><pubDate>Mon, 26 Aug 2019 21:00:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198519.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>187</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Silence of the Lambs with Brooke Smith]]></title><description><![CDATA[For the 100th and final (for now) episode of I Was There Too, Matt finally gets to sit down with his long-sought guest, actress Brooke Smith. She joins Matt to discuss her role as Catherine Martin aka the girl in the well in the 1991 horror film The Silence of the Lambs. Catherine chats about having to gain weight for the role, reading with three different actors all going out for the Jame “Buffalo Bill” Gumb role, and how director Jonathan Demme made her confront her demons. Plus, Matt bids farewell (for now) to all the wonderful listeners! This episode is brought to you by The Jim Jefferies Show Podcast.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198507</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Dec 2018 05:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198507.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2888</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Halloween 2018 with Toby Huss]]></title><description><![CDATA[The incredibly talented actor Toby Huss joins Matt to discuss his role as Ray Nelson in the 2018 slasher film Halloween. Toby talks about director David Gordon Green letting him improvise, being attacked by fire ants while filming, and how his character might have turned out to be deaf. Plus, Toby talks about his other various film and TV roles which include King of The Hill, Cowboys & Aliens, and the upcoming series Dickinson.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198521</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:05:06 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198521.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2732</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[IWTT Classic: Halloween with P.J. Soles]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress P.J. Soles joins Matt this week to talk about her role as Lynda van der Klok in the 1978 John Carpenter classic Halloween. P.J. talks about why the way she said “totally” secured her role in the film, what it’s like to shoot a sex & death scene all at once, and her thoughts on her legendary death scene being recreated at Halloween Horror Nights at Universal Studios. P.J. also tells us her experience working with Bill Murray on Stripes, how she had to wrestle Rod Stewart for the jacket she would use for Rock ‘n’ Roll High School, and working alongside a very friendly Harrison Ford on the made for TV film The Possessed. Plus, filmmaker Jay Cheel of The Film Junk Podcast helps Matt face his Halloween fears on location during I Was Literally There Too.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198523</guid><pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 21:00:40 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198523.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3900</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Casino Royale with Carlos Leal]]></title><description><![CDATA[Accomplished actor and rapper Carlos Leal joins Matt to discuss his role as Tournament Director in the 2006 James Bond film Casino Royale. Carlos shares never before told stories about his original role as the croupier, why he believed for 24 hours that he was going to be the villain after his audition, and falling asleep in his chair while filming. Plus, Carlos tells us the story he invented for his Tournament Director including why his mustache was so important.This episode is brought to you by The Jim Jefferies Show podcast.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198525</guid><pubDate>Tue, 23 Oct 2018 21:04:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198525.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2767</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Game of Thrones and Girl With The Dragon Tattoo with Tony Way]]></title><description><![CDATA[Matt is joined by the wonderful actor, Tony Way.  Tony chats about his time on Game of Thrones as Sir Dontos Hollard, his experience playing backgammon with Diana Rigg, and shares a very surprising I Wasn't There Too. So sit back, brew some tea and enjoy this very British episode of I Was There Too.  ]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198527</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Oct 2018 00:00:36 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198527.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4237</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[12 Years A Slave and Saturday Night Live with Taran Killam]]></title><description><![CDATA[Comedian, writer, and actor Taran Killam joins Matt to talk about his role as Hamilton in the 2013 period drama 12 Years A Slave and his time at Saturday Night Live. Taran chats about doing magic in an ultimately cut scene, director Steve McQueen giving a pillow a second take, and pushing for the top hat. Also, we hear about Taran’s audition experience for SNL, the inspiration behind the “Les Jeunes De Paris” & Mokiki sketches, and when he realized it was time to go. Plus, Taran tells us about his dream coming true with Arnold Schwarznegger starring in his film Killing Gunther, performing Hamilton on Broadway, and much more!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198529</guid><pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 21:03:26 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198529.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5324</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Transformers: Dark of the Moon with Andy Daly]]></title><description><![CDATA[The great Andy Daly joins Matt to discuss his role as Mailroom Worker in the 2011 film, Transformers: Dark of the Moon. Andy talks about auditioning for Michael Bay as the director sat on the floor, doing a product placement scene for an item Michael Bay referred to as “China milk,” and having a stuntman who looked nothing like him get slammed against a wall. Plus, we’ll hear some fun facts from some of Andy’s other roles in film and TV such as Semi-Pro, Eastbound and Down, as well as inventing Mustache TV.This episode is brought to you by Backblaze ( www.backblaze.com/iwtt ).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198531</guid><pubDate>Tue, 25 Sep 2018 21:03:11 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198531.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4046</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[JAWS with the People and Places of Amity Island]]></title><description><![CDATA[Matt goes out in the field to Amity&nbsp;Island itself, the beautiful Martha’s Vineyard, to talk to the locals about the 1975 blockbuster, Jaws. Join Matt as he visits the Jaws bridge location, an actor from the film, Chief Brody’s house, The Chappy Ferry, and more. There is even talk of a recent shark attack to add to the experience. Enjoy!This episode is brought to you by Warby Parker ( www.warbyparker.com/iwtt ).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198533</guid><pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2018 21:02:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198533.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2870</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Friday The 13th 13th Live at The Dynasty Typewriter Co-hosted by Paul Rust with Robbi Morgan, Melanie Kinnaman, and Shavar Ross]]></title><description><![CDATA[Matt and guest co-host Paul Rust are joined by actors Robbi Morgan, Melanie Kinnaman, and Shavar Ross of the Friday The 13th franchise live from the Dynasty Typewriter theater in Los Angeles! They talk about how Robbi feels about being the first of many deaths to kick off the franchise as Annie the hitchhiker, Shavar aka Reggie the Reckless not knowing he was going to film a horror film, and Melanie having to scream over and over again to get the perfect pitch for a scene. For more Friday The 13th discussion subscribe to “In Voorhees We Trust With Gourley and Rust” go to&nbsp; stitcherpremium.com/voorhees and use promo code ‘VOORHEES’ for 1 month free!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198535</guid><pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2018 23:37:19 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198535.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3531</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[In Voorhees We Trust With Gourley and Rust]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lace up your hiking boots and pick a bunk because your stay at Camp Crystal Lake is just beginning. In this free and full-length primer episode of 'In Voorhees We Trust With Gourley and Rust,' you’ll learn why Matt and Paul love the&nbsp;Friday the 13th&nbsp;franchise so much, what they expect to learn about themselves in revisiting it, and how they plan to tackle and assess all 12 films of the Voorhees family legacy. Join them on their journey to Crystal Lake, Manhattan, hell, and outer space beyond!For more In Voorhees We Trust, go to stitcherpremium.com/voorhees and use promo code 'VOORHEES’ for 1 month free!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198537</guid><pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2018 21:02:39 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198537.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>5525</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Was There Too For I Was There Too Part Too with Matt Gourley hosted by Ben Blacker]]></title><description><![CDATA[In part two of a special two-part episode,&nbsp;wonderful writer Ben Blacker (Hex Wives, Thrilling Adventure Hour) interviews Matt all about his experience hosting I Was There Too. Matt shares stories about the dream guests that got away, how he puts his guests at ease before interviewing them, and more as they look back at the some of the funny, weird, inspirational moments over the years.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198539</guid><pubDate>Tue, 14 Aug 2018 21:05:08 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198539.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3557</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Platoon, Saving Private Ryan, Band of Brothers and More with Captain Dale Dye]]></title><description><![CDATA[Veteran of the Vietnam war, actor, and technical advisor Dale Dye joins Matt to talk about how he became the military technical advisor for Platoon, Saving Private Ryan, Band of Brothers, and more. Dale talks about his mission to meet with Oliver Stone to help bring more realism to Hollywood films, how Oliver Stone helped him get the acting bug, and whether the squibs on Willem Dafoe in Platoon were intended to work or not. Plus, Matt completes a lifelong quest to find out the meaning of one of the Vietnam phrases used in Platoon. Brace yourself!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198541</guid><pubDate>Tue, 31 Jul 2018 21:02:24 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198541.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3990</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Was There Too for I Was There Too with Matt Gourley]]></title><description><![CDATA[In part one of a special two-part episode, wonderful writer Ben Blacker (Hex Wives, Thrilling Adventure Hour) interviews Matt all about his experience hosting I Was There Too. Matt shares where the idea for the show came from, his preparation process for interviewing his guests, and his dream guest list as they look back at the some of the funny, weird, inspirational moments over the years.This episode is brought to you by Shudder ( www.shudder.com/podcast code: IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198543</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jul 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198543.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3525</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Yeardley Smith Part II, The Legend of Billie Jean and More]]></title><description><![CDATA[The wonderful Yeardley Smith (The Simpsons, Small Town Dicks Podcast) returns to join Matt to discuss her role as Putter Jacks in the 1985 film The Legend of Billie Jean. Yeardley also talks about her experience as the sassy virgin secretary on Herman’s Head, her first film Heaven Help Us, and jumping onto the fast moving train that was Sports Night. Plus, she shares stories of roles she didn’t end up getting which include The Goonies, The Purple Rose of Cairo, and My Sister Sam.This episode is brought to you by You Can’t Make This Up podcast.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198545</guid><pubDate>Tue, 03 Jul 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198545.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3397</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Popeye and Sixteen Candles with Paul Dooley]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Paul Dooley joins Matt to talk about his roles as Wimpy in the 1980 film Popeye, as Jim Baker in the 1984 film Sixteen Candles, and a whole lot more. First, Paul discusses his approach to adapting the character of Wimpy, working alongside Robert Altman and Harry Nilsson, and improvising with his colleagues in their downtime. Then, we’ll find out which line from Sixteen Candles was changed by Paul for the better before getting stories about everything from partnering with a very serious Max von Sydow in Strange Brew to Paul’s voice work within the Cars franchise.This episode is sponsored by Netflix's You Can't Make This Up Podcast.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198547</guid><pubDate>Tue, 19 Jun 2018 21:00:58 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198547.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3410</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[City Slickers and The Simpsons with Yeardley Smith]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Yeardley Smith joins Matt to discuss her role as Nancy in the 1991 film City Slickers as well as being the voice of Lisa Simpson in The Simpsons. Yeardley talks about acting in Tom Stoppard’s The Real Thing in her early years, working with Stephen King, and the draw of the live stage. Plus, we’ll hear the story behind Homer’s voice change, tales from Mom’s on Strike, and the origin of Yeardley’s podcast Small Town Dicks.This episode is sponsored by Netflix's Arrested Development.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198549</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 May 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198549.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3622</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Was There Zoo with Animal Trainer Molly O’Neill]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress and animal trainer for film and TV Molly O’Neill joins Matt and guest co-host Amanda Lund to talk about being responsible for some of the great animal performances in cinema and TV history. Molly shares stories of working with direwolves on Game of Thrones, a runaway goat on the set of Gangster Squad, and a shitting monkey on a music video. Plus, Matt and Amanda ask Molly if their cat Margaux the Fat Guy has a potential acting career.This episode is brought to you by Simple Contacts ( www.simplecontacts.com/iwtt ).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198552</guid><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198552.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3364</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Space Jam, Ed Wood, and Everything Else with Maurice LaMarche]]></title><description><![CDATA[Legendary voice actor Maurice LaMarche joins Matt to talk about his voice over roles in Space Jam, Ed Wood, and the countless other great voice over performances in his career. Maurice tells us about doing the voice for Vincent D’Onofrio’s portrayal of Orson Welles in Tim Burton’s film Ed Wood, how Billy West helped him with the Pepe Le Pew role in Space Jam, and getting the role of Brain in Pinky and The Brain on the spot. Stick around for the outstanding burps at the end!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198554</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198554.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3789</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Almost Every Film Ever with Amy Nicholson and Jen Yamato]]></title><description><![CDATA[Film critics Amy Nicholson &amp; Jen Yamato join Matt to talk about what it’s like to be a critic in today’s film climate. They discuss everything from their approaches to criticism to the hardest movies to review. Plus, we’ll hear about how they manage relationships and conflicts of interest, the problem with review aggregators, and the weirdness of Walmart’s film festival before they get into their film critic diets.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198556</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198556.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3987</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scent Of A Woman with Jordan Katz]]></title><description><![CDATA[Trumpet player/banjo player/composer Jordan Katz (Drop the Mic) joins Matt and guest co-host Mark McConville to discuss being one of the students in the climactic school scene in 1992’s Scent of a Woman. Jordan talks about his experience watching Al Pacino reaching peak Pacino, getting scouted for the scene by someone’s mother who knew an agent in Long Island, and watching Philip Seymour Hoffman telling a whole room of teenagers to be quiet. Plus, Jordan shares why he was ultimately told to leave the set during the week of shooting.This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Mubi.com.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198558</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Mar 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198558.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2780</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Eyes Were There Too: Doctor Strange with Amy Landecker]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Amy Landecker joins Matt and guest co-host Amanda Lund to discuss her almost entirely cut role as an anesthesiologist in the 2016 Marvel film Doctor Strange. Amy describes what she expected from the project, the confusion that led to her character essentially being cut, and the one line of hers that made it in. Plus, she talks about working with the Coen Brothers on A Serious Man, bonding with the cast and crew of Transparent through “The Box,” and voice doubling for Julia Roberts.This episode is sponsored by&nbsp; Mack Weldon &nbsp;(code: IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198560</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Mar 2018 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198560.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3187</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and Big Fish with John August]]></title><description><![CDATA[Screenwriter and co-host of Scriptnotes podcast John August joins Matt to discuss the 2005 film Charlie and the Chocolate Factory and the 2003 film Big Fish. John talks about how he hadnt seen the 1971 Willy Wonka movie before writing the script, Johnny Depps original Alfred Hitchcock take on the Wonka character, and how his collaboration with Tim Burton started. Plus, John shares his process of method writing which helped him get in the right mindset while writing his new book Arlo Finch in the Valley of Fire. This episode is brought to you by Mubi.com (www.mubi.com/WasThere).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198562</guid><pubDate>Tue, 27 Feb 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198562.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2789</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Million Dollar Baby with Riki Lindhome]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Riki Lindhome joins Matt to discuss her role as Mardell Fitzgerald in the 2004 Best Picture winner Million Dollar Baby. Riki talks about what it was like to work with Clint Eastwood as both an actor and a director, her origins with The Actors Gang, and the amazing food on set. Plus, Riki discusses her other projects such as The Last House on the Left and Buffy the Vampire Slayer as well as finding success through casting director workshops. This episode is sponsored by MUBI.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198564</guid><pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198564.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3581</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Looper with Noah Segan]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Noah Segan returns this week and joins Matt to discuss his role as Kid Blue in the 2012 film Looper. Noah talks about how he ended up in the film, the origin of his nick name Kid Blue which existed before the film, and the story behind dropping his gun while twirling it. Plus, we hear about the incredible makeup work that went into Joseph Gordon-Levitts transformation into Bruce Willis. This episode is brought to you by Mubi (www.mubi.com/WasThere).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198566</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Jan 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198566.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2894</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Last Jedi with Noah Segan]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Noah Segan joins Matt this week to discuss his role as X-wing fighter pilot Stomeroni Starck in the 2017 film Star Wars: Episode VIII - The Last Jedi. Noah talks about how he got the role, the origin of the name Stomeroni Starck and the connection to Poe Dameron, and becoming emotional while touring the Millennium Falcon. Plus, Noah shares how he became good friends with director Rian Johnson and has been lucky enough to be a part of his many projects.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198568</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Jan 2018 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198568.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2853</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Scrooged with Dick Blasucci and Co-host Maria Blasucci]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writer, producer, and Maria Blasuccis dad Dick Blasucci joins Matt and Maria to discuss his role as the IBC Television Executive in the 1988 Christmas film Scrooged. Dick explains how his friendship with Bill Murray landed him the role and shares stories of their outings together during their Second City days. Later, Dick recalls working alongside the Solid Gold Dancers before hinting at an SCTV reunion in the works, and top secret guest Starship 1 returns to give a spirited take on Star Wars: The Last Jedi.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198570</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198570.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3504</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Wasn't There Too: Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Squeakquel with Amanda Lund, Maria Blasucci, and Sara Sposito]]></title><description><![CDATA[Its another edition of I Wasnt There Too featuring the on-set voices of the Chipettes from Alvin and the Chipmunks: The Squeakquel, Amanda Lund, Maria Blasucci, and Sara Sposito. The girls give a sampling of their chipmunk voices before getting into stories about who they bonded with on set, drama between PAs, and what it was like filming on the Universal backlot. Plus, we hear about their problems with lateness before the Chipettes share what they learned from the experience. This episode is sponsored by HelloFresh (code: IWTT30).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198572</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Dec 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198572.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2979</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Star Trek with Brandon Adams]]></title><description><![CDATA[Background actor Brandon Adams joins Matt this week to discuss his role as a guy on the shuttle - aka Jim Shuttle - in the 2009 Star Trek reboot. Brandon talks about having his face featured right alongside the films stars in the trailer, the joke he made to J.J. Abrams that he thought would get him fired, and the lengths he had to go to in order to fulfill his NDA. Plus, Brandon shares the story of how he became best friends with Chris Pine while working on set. This episode is sponsored by HelloFresh (code: IWTT30) and Casper Mattresses (code: IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198574</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Nov 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198574.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2513</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Django Unchained and Get Out with Marcus Henderson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor, chess teacher, great storyteller Marcus Henderson joins Matt to discuss his roles in Quentin Tarantinos Django Unchained and Jordan Peeles Get Out. He tells us about his Django audition in which he pretended to be attacked by a dog, the layers he went into in portraying Groundskeeper Walter in Get Out, and running to the point of injury for Get Out. Plus, Marcus shares a memorable encounter with Samuel L. Jackson. This episode is brought to you by Hello Fresh (www.hellofresh.com code: IWTT30).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198576</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Nov 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198576.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2899</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Meatballs with Russ Banham]]></title><description><![CDATA[Author and director Russ Banham joins Matt and guest co-host Steve Agee to discuss his role as Bobby Crockett in the 1979 classic comedy Meatballs. Russ tells of how his unusual wardrobe helped him during his audition before sharing stories of filming in a real summer camp and working alongside Bill Murray. Later, Russ talks about transitioning from acting into writing as well as how he ended up alongside the Rolling Stones on an episode of&nbsp;Saturday&nbsp;Night Live.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198578</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 Oct 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198578.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2584</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Twin Peaks with Eric Edelstein and guest co-host Steve Berg]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Eric Edelstein joins Matt and guest co-host Steve Berg to discuss his role as Detective Smiley Fusco in the 2017 return of Twin Peaks. Eric tells of how he went from being a fan of the original series to having a role in the return written specifically for him, what it was like to engage in Transcendental Meditation with David Lynch, and his experiences acting opposite Kyle MacLachlan. Plus, the three Drunk History vets reminisce about their respective appearances on the comedy program. This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon (code: WASTHERE) and Hello Fresh (code: IWTT30).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198580</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Oct 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198580.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3623</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Catwoman with Janet Varney]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress and improviser Janet Varney joins Matt to discuss her role as Party Girl in the 2004 superhero film Catwoman. Janet tells us whether shooting party scenes are as bad as being at a party with people you dont know, crying on the drive home at 5am, and running into someone from her childhood on set. Plus, we hear how Janet had to pretend to be invisible for a pre-read for the role of Invisible Woman in Fantastic Four. This episode is brought to you by Audible (www.audible.com/WASTHERE) and Mindshow (www.mindshow.com).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198582</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Sep 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198582.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2608</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[RoboCop with Kevin Page]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Kevin Page joins Matt to discuss his role as Kinney in the 1987 action film RoboCop. Kevin talks about having to choose between continuing theatre or taking the role and what it was like getting obliterated by ED-209 and becoming the most squibbed man in film history. Plus, Kevin tells us about using a robot for an art gallery he owned for a couple of years and his role as Stu Chermack on Seinfeld. This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Hello Fresh (www.hellofresh.com code: IWTT30).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198584</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Sep 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198584.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2423</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Legally Blonde with Alanna Ubach]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Alanna Ubach joins Matt and guest co-host Amanda Lund this week to discuss her role as Serena in the 2001 comedy Legally Blonde. Alanna shares how Jessica Cauffiel helped her book the role by having her mirror her movements, improvising her Vietnamese line, and being an adopted blonde. Plus, we hear Alanna answer important questions like Why was Warner such a dork?, as she answers questions asked by Matts parents.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198586</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Aug 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198586.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2644</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[True Detective with Azure Parsons]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Azure Parsons joins Matt this week to discuss her role as Charmaine Boudreaux on the hit television series "True Detective." She tells Matt about her first reaction to reading her part as well as the strategies she took to enmesh herself into such a dark mindset. Then, she shares the unusual way in which she nabbed the role and her recollections of run-ins with Woody Harrelson. Later, Matt gets fellow "True Detective" actors Christopher Berry and Dave Davis on the line to talk about getting roughed up by Matthew McConaughey and how they landed on the right motivations for their characters. This episode is brought to you by HelloFresh (www.hellofresh.com code: IWTT30)]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198588</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198588.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4027</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Close Encounters of the Third Kind with Cary Guffey]]></title><description><![CDATA[In anticipation of the 40th anniversary, former child actor Cary Guffey joins Matt to share his memories of playing little Barry Guiler in Stephen Spielberg's 1977 classic Close Encounters of the Third Kind. Cary discusses what it was like to act in a movie before he'd seen one and explains how he earned the nickname "One Take Cary." Then, he tells the story of how he called out Richard Dreyfuss for missing a line during a scene, shares what it was like to be a part of the cultural zeitgeist from such a young age, and reveals the incident that made him decide to give up acting. This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Audible (www.audible.com/WASTHERE).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198589</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198589.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2521</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[True Lies with Tom Arnold]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor and comedian Tom Arnold joins Matt to give us a behind the scenes look on what it was like working alongside Arnold Schwarzenegger in the James Cameron 1994 action film True Lies. Tom tells us about how he ended up bonding with Arnold and James in his audition for the role of Albert Gib Gibson, many of his ad-libs making it into the final cut of the film, and James making a reluctant Arnold do a dangerous stunt by doing it in front of him. Plus, Tom confirms some trivia surrounding the movie as he plays Confirm or Deny: IMDB Trivia. This episode is brought to you by Hello Fresh (www.hellofresh.com code: IWTT30) and Bombfell (www.bombfell.com/IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198590</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198590.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2397</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2 with Steve Agee]]></title><description><![CDATA[Matt is back from his honeymoon to interview Steve Agee about his role as Gef the Ravager in the 2017 Marvel film Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2. In a I Was There Too first, Matt and Steve have a pre-interview before watching the film together. Among many great stories Steve reveals about his time on the film such as Stallone in the bridge chair, catching on fire himself, and getting beer squibbed.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198591</guid><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198591.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3515</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ghostbusters with Michael Ensign and guest hosted by Mark McConville]]></title><description><![CDATA[While Matt is off getting married and honeymooned, I Was There Too will feature a special run of guest hosted episodes! This week actor Michael Ensign joins guest host Mark McConville to discuss the 1984 film Ghostbusters. Michael tells us about the multiple takes of his scene as the Hotel Manager due to the improvisation from the rest of the cast, his character standing up to Peter Venkman, and not realizing the popularity of the film until watching it in a theater with an audience saying the lines. He also talks about his time with the Royal Shakespeare Company, his first big film role in Midnight Express, and his many other film/TV credits including Titanic, The Dukes of Hazzard, and much more.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198592</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198592.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3059</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Rebel Without a Cause with Jack Grinnage and guest hosted by Amanda Lund and Maria Blasucci]]></title><description><![CDATA[While Matt is off getting married and honeymooned, I Was There Too will feature a special run of guest hosted episodes! This week actor Jack Grinnage joins guest hosts Amanda Lund and Maria Blasucci to discuss the 1955 film Rebel Without a Cause. Jack explains how he lied about his age to get a role in the movie, his college friendship with actress Beverly Long, and how they built the action around James Deans strengths. Then, they talk about the evolution of craft services, why everyone wanted to be paid for golden time, and how a terrible interview got Jack cast in King Creole. Finally, Jack tells of meeting Colonel Tom Parker, why he never saw Elvis out of makeup, and Laurence Oliviers reaction to finding Jack in his chair during the filming of Spartacus. This episode is brought to you by Harry's (www.harrys.com/IWTT) and HelloFresh (www.hellofresh.com&nbsp;code: IWTT30).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198593</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Jun 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198593.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3518</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Every Star Wars Movie with Peter Mayhew and guest hosted by Ben Blacker!]]></title><description><![CDATA[While Matt is off getting married and honeymooned, I Was There Too will feature a special run of guest hosted episodes! This week actor Peter Mayhew joins guest host Ben Blacker to discuss playing Chewbacca in every Star Wars movie. Peter tells us about how a photo of him in a local paper lead to him getting the role of a minotaur in Sinbad and the Eye of the Tiger, receiving a phone calls months later being offered a role in a little movie called Star Wars, his working relationship with Harrison Ford, the different directing styles of George Lucas and J.J. Abrams, finding the roar, and much more. Its a must listen for any Star Wars fan!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198594</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198594.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3461</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Ant-Man and Prisoners with David Dastmalchian and guesthosted by Steve Agee!]]></title><description><![CDATA[While Matt is off getting married and honeymooned, I Was There Too will feature a special run of guest hosted episodes! This week actor David Dastmalchian joins guest host Steve Agee to discuss the 2013 thriller Prisoners and the 2015 superhero film Ant-Man. David tells us about being very grateful about landing the part of Bob Taylor in Prisoners, thinking he had actually hurt Jake Gyllenhaal during filming, and being thankful to director Denis Villeneuve for the opportunity to be a part of Blade Runner 2049. Then, David talks about the many improvised lines during the filming of Ant-Man, contributing to his characters wardrobe &amp; love of Elvis, and tricking Paul Rudd into believing he was actually Russian. Plus, David and Steve bond over similar circumstances when it came to testing to become a part of the Marvel family. This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Harrys (www.harrys.com/IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198595</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 May 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198595.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4176</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Collected Stories Vol. 3: The Best of I Was There Too]]></title><description><![CDATA[Once again Matt has lovingly pieced together a collection of the best anecdotes told on I Was There Too about experiences on the set of the Star Wars trilogy, Back to The Future, Die Hard, and many more. Youll hear from Steven de Souza, Tom Wilson, Lauren Lapkus, Ahmed Best, Jimmy Pardo, and more on topics ranging from beating Michael Jackson for the role of Jar Jar Binks to down to the wire re-shoots for Die Hard. Plus, Matt checks in with Starship 1, the mysterious real person that auditioned for Star Wars Episode 8: The Last Jedi to hear her real time reaction of the trailer and some of the moments from the Star Wars Celebration in Orlando. This episode is brought to you by Generation Tux (www.generationtux.com code: IWTT), Harrys (www.harrys.com/iwtt), and Blue Apron (www.blueapron.com/iwastheretoo).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198596</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Apr 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198596.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3522</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Star Wars Prequel Trilogy with Ahmed Best]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Ahmed Best joins Matt for a jumbo sized episode of I Was There Too to discuss playing Jar Jar Binks in The Star Wars Prequel Trilogy. Recorded live from Largo at the Coronet as well as the Earwolf studio, Ahmed tells us about the many stand in roles he played during the filming of the films, being pulled from the cast of Stomp in San Francisco, and contributing his own ideas on what the iconic Yoda lightsaber battle should look like purely as a fan of Star Wars. Plus, we find out if Ahmed really suffered severe burns from hot tea being spilled on his lap and if he really beat out Michael Jackson in a role during Confirm or Dispel Dubious IMDB Trivia. Stay tuned after the interview for a preview for an upcoming podcast mini-series by Matt entitled ‘The Complete Man,’ a spin-off of Amanda Lund’s brilliant podcast ‘The Complete Woman.’ Find it on Stitcher Premium.This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Audible (www.audible.com/wasthere).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198509</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 07:05:53 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198509.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4081</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kong: Skull Island with Marc Evan Jackson]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a first for I Was There Too, Matt ventures outside his home to watch a movie still in theaters, Kong: Skull Island. He is joined by the incredible Marc Evan Jackson who talks about his role in the film as Landsat Steve. If you havent seen the film, shower, get dressed, get in your car, go the theater, watch the film, and listen to this episode! Stay tuned after the interview for a preview for an upcoming podcast mini-series by Amanda Lund, a follow up to her brilliant podcast 'The Complete Woman' entitled 'Complete Joy.' Find it on Stitcher Premium:&nbsp;http://stitcherpremium.com/complete This episode is brought to you by Audible (www.audible.com/wasthere) and Blue Apron (www.blueapron.com/iwastheretoo).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198597</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198597.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3045</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Running Man and Die Hard with Steven de Souza: Live from Alamo Drafthouse]]></title><description><![CDATA[Presented by the Alamo Drafthouse and recorded live from The Regent Theater in Downtown Los Angeles, Matt speaks with screenwriter Steven de Souza about the 1987 film The Running Man and 1988 film Die Hard. Steven lays urban myths to rest and goes in depth about both films including the unavoidable political aspects of the now 30 year old film The Running Man compared to todays political climate and the ever changing script almost down to the wire of Die Hard. Plus, we hear a bit how the cult classic Hudson Hawk become what it is thanks to Bruce Willis input. This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Hullo (www.hullopillow.com/IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198598</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Mar 2017 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198598.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3500</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[More Back To The Future with Jeffrey Weissman]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Jeffrey Weissman joins Matt this week to discuss his unique experience of playing George McFly in Back to the Future Part II and III after Crispin Glover left the films. Jeffrey tells us about the mix of acting and impression that went along with playing the role, being in a weird place as the new replacement on set, and hearing Crispins thoughts using his likeness. We also hear about Jeffreys other roles in&nbsp;Clint Eastwoods Pale Rider, Johnny Dangerously, Twilight Zone: The Movie, and Saved by the Bell.&nbsp;Plus, writers Ben Acker and Ben Blacker of The Thrilling Adventure Hour join Matt to talk about&nbsp;their novel, 'Star Wars Join the Resistance,' what its like to work with the Lucasfilm story group, and Matt becoming part of the Star Wars canon. This episode is brought to you by Hullo (www.hullopillow.com/IWTT).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198599</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Mar 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198599.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2848</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Back to the Future Trilogy with Tom Wilson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor and artist Tom Wilson joins Matt this week to discuss being present (but also past and future) in the Back to the Future Trilogy as Biff Tannen, among other members of the Tannen clan. Tom tells us about finding a creative way to approach being asked the same questions about the films, which includes creating a handy postcard to present to anyone on the street that asks him the same questions over and over. We also hear what it was like for him - as someone who was bullied - to play a bully himself, being paired off to rehearse his scenes with Crispin Glover, and what he believes to be the heart of all the movies. Plus, Tom talks about being on a debate team with David Brooks of the NY Times, the inspiration for his Pop Fugue' paintings, and various roles hes played over the years including one of his earliest on The Facts of Life. Los Angeles: On February 28th there will be a LIVE I Was There Too at The Regent Theater with legendary screenwriter Steven de Souza (Die Hard, Commando) along with a screening of The Running Man (celebrating its 30th Anniversary). Get tickets at http://www.theregenttheater.com This episode is brought to you by Blue Apron (www.blueapron.com/IWasThereToo). Biffs Question Song https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=WmjYimspW-4]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198600</guid><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198600.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2932</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dreamgirls with Jimmy Pardo]]></title><description><![CDATA[In another edition of I Wasnt There Too, professional comedian and Never Not Funny host Jimmy Pardo joins Matt to talk about being cut from the 2006 musical drama Dreamgirls. Jimmy goes deep into how his role of comedian was offered to him out of the blue, befriending an extra while being on set for 13 hours to shoot his one line, and when he heard the news of when his role was cut. Plus, Jimmy tells us about being cut out of The Informant!, Bob Odenkirk giving him a push to do stand-up comedy when he still worked in a record store, and his time doing warm up for Conan. This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE) and Blue Apron (www.blueapron.com/IWASTHERETOO)]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198601</guid><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198601.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3294</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inception and Avatar with Dileep Rao]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Dileep Rao has had the pleasure of working with auteur filmmakers Sam Raimi, James Cameron, and Christopher Nolan. Dileep joins Matt this week to talk about playing Yusuf, the dream chemist in Christopher Nolans 2010 film Inception and Dr. Patel in James Camerons 2009 film Avatar. He also comments on the validity of the Inception fan theories, being able to come to James Cameron with additions to his character, and how working with Sam Raimi on Drag Me to Hell was like working with family. Plus, a discussion on goat castration. Happy New Year! This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE)]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198602</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Jan 2017 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198602.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2904</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Star Wars Holiday Special with Larry Heider]]></title><description><![CDATA[Celebrate the true holiday of the season, The Wookiee Life Day with Matt and special guest and professional camera man Larry Heider who has worked on countless TV projects including the infamous and wonderful Star Wars Holiday Special from 1978. Join them as they discuss how this special came to be including what Larry observed behind the scenes and all the great photos he took along the way. Plus, one more special visit from Starship 1, the mysterious real person that did audition for Star Wars: Episode 8. All photos are property of Larry Heider and may not be used without written consent. All rights reserved]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198603</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198603.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3227</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Almost Famous with Marc Maron: Live from Now Hear This]]></title><description><![CDATA[Live from the Now Hear This Festival, actor, author, cat lover, and vanguard podcaster Marc Maron joins Matt to talk about his role as the Angry Promoter in the 2000 Cameron Crowe film Almost Famous. Marc tells us all about the pants his character wears, how his scene has now since established a catchprhase in the intro of his popular podcast WTF with Marc Maron, and why this role fits just right in his personal range as an actor. He also talks about his cats Monkey &amp; LaFonda, what its like to prepare for an interview with Neil Young, and the now infamous Gallagher mid-interview walk out. Plus, Matts old college buddy and author Tyler Dilts joins Matt to talk about how WTF and I Was There Too are big influences in his detective novels. This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon (www.mackweldon.com code: WASTHERE).]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198604</guid><pubDate>Wed, 07 Dec 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198604.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3540</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The 50th Episode Squib Spectacular]]></title><description><![CDATA[On this very special 50th episode of I Was There Too, Matt invites you all along on his journey to fulfill a lifelong dream of getting professionally squibbed. Substitute host and podcast brethren Mark McConville interviews Matt and andrew from J&amp;M Special Effects throughout the process and fellow podcast soulmates Paul F. Tompkins and Jeremy Carter beautifully provide the taut action drama of the fictional scenario in which Matt is to be fake shot. Plus, Matts dad, stepmom, and fiancée join him to provide a tough but honest critical reaction. This episode is brought to you by Stamps.com. THE SQUIBBENING DOCUMENTARY BY JAY CHEEL THE SQUIBBENING from Jay Cheel on Vimeo.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198605</guid><pubDate>Wed, 23 Nov 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198605.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2319</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Return Of The Jedi with Kevin Thompson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Yub nub! On the final of three very special Star Wars trilogy episodes of I Was There Too, Matt is joined by Kevin Thompson who played the Ewoks Chubbray and Paploo in the original 1983 film Return Of The Jedi. Kevin tells us how he went from being a street mime to auditioning for the movie, how they shot swinging off the speeder bike, and the true danger that comes from being in the stunt world. He also talks about his role as Bear in the 1982 film Blade Runner and his reaction to finally getting his own Star Wars action figure. Plus, yet another classic Star Wars Superego sketch! This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon and Stamps.com.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198606</guid><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198606.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3534</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Bonus Episode: The Empire Strikes Back: Controversy Averted]]></title><description><![CDATA[On a very important bonus episode of I Was There Too, we will finally have the answer to the question asked last episode: Who physically played the body of The Emperor in the original version of The Empire Strikes Back? We know that Cio-Cio the chimp was used for the superimposed eyes of The Emperor. But did Elaine Baker or Marjorie Eaton ultimately appear onscreen? Matt shares some new information and interviews Cio-Cio the chimp to finally put this mystery to rest.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198607</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Nov 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198607.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>510</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Empire Strikes Back with Clive Revill]]></title><description><![CDATA[On the second of three very special Star Wars trilogy episodes of I Was There Too, Matt is joined by Clive Revill who voices The Emperor in the pre-special edition 1980 film The Empire Strikes Back. Clive tells us about how director Irvin Kershner reached out to him for the role, finding the voice for The Emperor, and his thoughts on the final physical representation. Then, expert witnesses Pete the Retailer and Alex Robinson of the Star Wars Minute podcast join Matt to figure out who and actually what played the body of The Emperor during a new segment called Was I There Too?&nbsp;Plus, another classic Star Wars Superego sketch! This episode is brought to you by Stamps.com. THE ORIGINAL FOOTAGE:&nbsp; https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rKtciRCVpFE EXHIBIT 1: https://www.amazon.com/Making-Star-Wars-Empire-Strikes/dp/0345509617 EXHIBIT 2: http://x3rxe5.tumblr.com/post/148866162957/all-hail-the-chimperor-prior-to-beginning-return EXHIBIT 3: http://boards.theforce.net/threads/marjorie-eaton-the-original-emperor.50033425/ EXHIBIT 4: See the pics posted on this page.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198608</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198608.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3311</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Star Wars with Anthony Forrest]]></title><description><![CDATA[On the first of three very special Star Wars trilogy episodes of I Was There Too, Matt is joined by Anthony Forrest who plays the sand trooper mind-tricked by Obi-Wan Kenobi at the Mos Eisley roadblock who said 'These arent the droids were looking for,' in George Lucas 1977 film Star Wars. Anthony tells us how he was cast as the sand trooper after also being cast as Luke Skywalkers friend Fixer in the deleted scenes from the film, not being able to see a thing in the helmet, and getting to work with Lucas, Guinness, and Hamill. We also hear tales of rubbing elbows with Roger Moore in the James Bond film The Spy Who Loved Me and getting to see John Lennon and Yoko Ono during their 'Bed-In for Peace' campaign. Later, top secret guest Starship 1 returns to talk more about her audition for Star Wars: Episode 8. Plus, a classic Star Wars Superego sketch! Come see us at the Now Hear This podcast festival: nowhearthisfest.com This episode is brought to you by Mack Weldon and Nuisance Committee.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198609</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Oct 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198609.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3065</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Diamonds Are Forever with Putter Smith]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jazz and Bass veteran Putter Smith joins Matt this week to talk about playing the assassin Mr. Kidd in one of Matts all time favorite Bond films, Diamonds Are Forever. Well hear how he ended up getting a script for the film and doing a screen test with Paul Williams, getting to carry Sean Connery alongside fellow assassin Mr. Wint portrayed by Bruce Glover, and getting his arms burned for his death scene. Putter also tells us what it was like working with Thelonious Monk and the sessions for The Righteous Brothers Youve Lost That Lovin Feelin. Do yourself a favor and check out Tyler Dilts book in his homicide series Come Twilight which features references to this very podcast! This episode is brought to you by Stamps.com.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198610</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Sep 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198610.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2699</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Jurassic World with Lauren Lapkus]]></title><description><![CDATA[Is there a guest as wonderful as Lauren Lapkus? Probably not. Lauren joins Matt to talk about playing Vivian, one of the control room workers dealing with the chaos that unravels in Jurassic World. We hear about how Lauren had to get NASA clearance to shoot her scenes, what it's like to be in a mega-blockbuster, and her experience auditioning for Star Wars Episode 8. As a bonus, Lauren tells us what it was like working alongside Joe Pesci and Don Rickles in a Snickers commercial. Later, Matt shares an exclusive and deep cover interview with a secret guest who also auditioned for Star Wars Episode 8. Plus, Matt answers listener questions in the return of I Was There Q&amp;A! The Strangely Cruel and Unusual Death in Jurassic World:&nbsp; http://birthmoviesdeath.com/2015/06/15/the-strangely-cruel-and-unusual-death-in-jurassic-world The James Bond Stunt Spectacular That Never Was: http://www.themeparkinsider.com/flume/201410/4241/ Come see us at the Now Hear This podcast festival: nowhearthisfest.com This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon and Stamps.com.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198611</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Sep 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198611.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2813</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Beverly Hills Cop and Willow with Rick Overton]]></title><description><![CDATA[Rick Overton walked into his audition for Beverly Hills Cop and director Martin Brest asked him about a prophylactic. Why? He's still not sure. Rick joins Matt to talk about doing martial arts with Eddie Murphy on set, preparing for his role of Bonded Warehouse Night Manager with mirror douche work, and getting to improvise in the film. Then, we hear of Rick's experience playing Franjean, a brownie who serves as comic relief in Willow's journey, why Million Dollar Mystery fell apart, and getting squibbed in Blind Fury. Come see us at the Now Hear This podcast festival: nowhearthisfest.com]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198612</guid><pubDate>Wed, 31 Aug 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198612.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2285</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Shawshank Redemption with Clancy Brown]]></title><description><![CDATA[Accomplished actor Clancy Brown joins Matt to talk about his role as the tough as nails prison guard Captain Hadley in the 1994 Frank Darabont film The Shawshank Redemption. They chat about how Clancys difficulty saying some of his character's colorful dialogue in the audition eventually got him the gig, why he turned down offers to work with correctional officers to help him with his role, and really hanging Tim Robbins over the ledge of a rooftop. Plus, we'll hear stories from the set of LOST, Sean Connery offering Clancy wisdom while filming Highlander, and Shakespeare being quoted on the set of Dukes of Hazzard. This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon and Adam and Eve.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198613</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Aug 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198613.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2512</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goldfinger with Linda Gidley]]></title><description><![CDATA[It's no secret that Matt is a huge James Bond fan. He hosts the James Bonding podcast along with fellow 007 fanatic Matt Mira and is very excited to dig into one of the most classic Bond films of all time, 1964's Goldfinger. Matt is joined by Linda Gidley for a discussion on what lead a young woman not even old enough to drive at the time to become one of Pussy Galore's Flying Circus Pilots in Goldfinger. Plus, Matt takes us through the 007's that never were in the return of the classic segment "I Wasn't There Too." This episode is sponsored by the Found podcast and Adam and Eve. JAMES BROLIN 007 SCREEN TEST: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=HxjyZ3lb8dc SAM NEILL 007 SCREEN TEST: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=rfGz-_iI23g]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198614</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Aug 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198614.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2745</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[(More) Grease with Jamie Donnelly]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jamie Donnelly aka "Brush-a Brush-a Brush-a" Jan the Pink Lady is back to talk more about the 1978 musical Grease. We'll hear if Jan was a snacker onstage as much as she was in the film, what would be the future of all the Grease characters, and possible inspiration for the end of the film. Plus, Jamie shares stories of stagnant LA river water, Seabreeze shammies, and Johnny Depp finger kisses. This episode is sponsored by Blue Apron, Casper Mattresses, and Now Hear This Podcast Festival.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198615</guid><pubDate>Wed, 20 Jul 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198615.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2702</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Collected Stories Vol. 2: The Best of I Was There Too]]></title><description><![CDATA[Matt gathered some of the best anecdotes told on I Was There Too about experiences on the set of Aliens, The Big Lebowski, Poltergeist, and many more. You'll hear from Paul F. Tompkins, Aimee Mann, Gilbert Gottfried, Lisa Jakub, Phil LaMarr and more on topics ranging from food, flesh, and pancakes to making &amp; breaking comedy. It's a perfect way to jump into the podcast for new listeners and a grand collection of great stories for regular listeners to revisit. This episode is sponsored by Squarespace, Blue Apron, and Now Hear This Podcast Festival.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198616</guid><pubDate>Wed, 06 Jul 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198616.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2909</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Carrie and The Hustler with Piper Laurie]]></title><description><![CDATA[One of America's best and most versatile actresses Piper Laurie joins Matt to talk about initially approaching the role of Carrie's mother in Brian De Palma's Carrie as a comedy, her experience working alongside Paul Newman and George C. Scott in the 1961 film The Hustler, and many other gems from her fantastic autobiography 'Learning to Live Out Loud: A Memoir.' Plus, Amanda Lund joins Matt to share a special talent that will enhance your listening enjoyment of certain songs in the return of I Was There Tune. This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon, Blue Apron, and Casper Mattresses.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198617</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jun 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198617.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2464</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Grease with Jamie Donnelly and Barry Pearl]]></title><description><![CDATA[Jamie Donnelly and Barry Pearl portrayed Pink Lady Jan and T-Bird Doody respectively from the 1978 musical Grease but did you know that they've been performing Grease in the theatrical production prior to the film? Jamie and Barry join Matt this week to talk about auditioning for their film roles, the fly by during "Beauty School Dropout," the intense heat as they shot the gymnasium scene, restoring the laughs from the theatrical production, and much more. This sponsored by Mack Weldon and Squarespace.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198618</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jun 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198618.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2870</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[They Live with Peter Jason]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prolific actor Peter Jason has a million stories about John Carpenter's cult classic They Live, Deadwood, and so much more. He joins Matt to talk about what it was like for his character Gilbert the Resistance Leader to get squibbed, the levels of Godhood in David Milch's John from Cincinnati, and Con Stapleton's submarine monologue from Deadwood. Plus, we hear how Peter got "t-boned" by Orson Welles. Check out the art on Earwolf.com by Andy Taylor!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198619</guid><pubDate>Wed, 25 May 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198619.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2716</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aliens Live Q&A with Carrie Henn, Ricco Ross, Jenette Goldstein]]></title><description><![CDATA[Presented by the Alamo Drafthouse and recorded live from The Ace Theater in Downtown Los Angeles, Matt hosts a special Alien Day Q&amp;A with Aliens stars Ricco Ross (Private Frost), Jenette Goldstein (Private Vasquez), and Carrie Henn (Newt). Plus, in honor of the great H.R. Giger, Matt shares a sketch from Superego where H.R. Giger takes his very suburban family through a fast food establishment drive-thru. This episode is sponsored by Mack Weldon, Squarespace, and Harold Ramis Film School.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198620</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198620.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2480</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Dead Poet's Society with Kurt Leitner]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor Kurt Leitner played Lester, one of the students in the classroom of Dead Poet's Society, a film that was highly influential for Matt. Kurt tells us about going from being a body double on set to becoming one of the supporting poets, organically coming up with the name Lester for his character as well as the character name of Spaz, his chicken walk making it into the trailer, and why his character didn't stand on a desk in support of Mr. Keating. Plus, we hear about the truly once in a lifetime experience of being directed&nbsp; in a playground atmosphere by Peter Weir and improvising with Robin Williams.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198621</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 Apr 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198621.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3395</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Revenant with Joshua Burge]]></title><description><![CDATA[Joshua Burge is one of the nicest human beings on this Earth. He joins Matt this week to talk about his role as Stubby Bill in The Revenant. Joshua tells us about auditioning for&nbsp;Alejandro Iñárritu&nbsp; learning how to shoot flintlocks, throw axes, and ride horses through survival bootcamp, the origin of the name Stubby Bill, and having a call and response with Tom Hardy's character on set. Plus, in honor of the infamous CGI bear in The Revenant, Matt counts down his Top 3 Emotive Acting Moments Done with Computer Graphics.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198622</guid><pubDate>Wed, 13 Apr 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198622.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2953</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Big Lebowski and Magnolia Live Show with Aimee Mann and Paul F. Tompkins]]></title><description><![CDATA[Recorded Live aboard the JoCo Cruise, Matt welcomes singer-songwriter Aimee Mann to talk about her role as Nihilist Woman, Franz's Girlfriend in The Big Lebowski. Aimee tells us about having to create dialogue in German, what it was like working with the Coen brothers, and whether or not her character gave her toe away willingly. Then, Paul F. Tompkins returns to talk about playing customer service operator Chad in Magnolia. Paul describes his three intense days of shooting the scene which included singing Sade songs with Mary Lynn Rajskub, embarrassing himself at the table read as he sat right next to Tom Cruise, and realizing his only his voice would make the final cut. Plus, Matt and Paul share how the power of the internet lead to them being friends and collaborators as they answer audience questions!]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198623</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Mar 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198623.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3251</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aladdin with Gilbert Gottfried]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gilbert Gottfried is the most wonderful tornado you can ever imagine. He joins Matt this week to talk about his role as Iago the parrot in Disney's Aladdin. Gilbert tells us about the audition process, having to re-record dialogue for the animated series that was deemed too dirty by a viewer, and the remarkable story of how a family reached their autistic son through a puppet of the parrot. Plus, Matt's Superego pals Mark McConville and Jeremy Carter talk about playing parts in Aladdin in a totally different context during I Was Par-rot Too.]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198624</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Mar 2016 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198624.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3354</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[E.T. The Extra Terrestrial with Sean Frye]]></title><description><![CDATA[The final chapter in the Spielberg Saga is here as Sean Frye joins Matt to talk about playing Steve, Elliot's older brother's friend in E.T. The Extra Terrestrial. Sean shares some great insight on all of the scenes from the film as well as what it was like working with Henry Thomas, E.T. himself, and going over to Harrison Ford's house. Plus, Matt gets a little crabby as he counts down his Top 10 List of Things That Happen in Movies That Never Happen in Real Life. HENRY THOMAS AUDITIONS FOR E.T. https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=tA5giyG8E7g SONG FOR YOU FAR AWAY BY JAMES TAYLOR https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x8YlrmBFn8s SOMEONE IN THE DARK BY MICHAEL JACKSON https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=0GYsRC-7_S0 TURN ON YOUR HEART LIGHT BY NEIL DIAMOND https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=m0TfR9mgOiU]]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198625</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Mar 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198625.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3015</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Raiders of the Lost Ark with Martin Casella]]></title><description><![CDATA[Part Two of the Three Part Spielberg-Aganza-Palooza continues with a discussion of 1981's Raiders of the Lost Ark. Martin Casella once again joins Matt to talk about his experience as Steven Spielberg's assistant on the film. Martin provides some wonderful insight on what went on behind the scenes including the origin of Marion's famous dress, Spielberg's must-see-TV habits, and what lead to the inception of E.T. Plus, Matt's companion from the Superego podcast, Jeremy Carter, joins him to talk about the iconic Indiana Jones jacket and his own personal quest to find the perfect fit in a new segment called 'I Was Wear Too.']]></description><link>http://www.earwolf.com/show/i-was-there-too/</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198626</guid><pubDate>Wed, 17 Feb 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198626.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3243</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Poltergeist with Martin Casella]]></title><description><![CDATA[Season 2 of I Was There Too with Matt Gourley begins with a discussion of 1982's Poltergeist, the 1st film in the IWTT Steven Spielberg Extravaganza! Martin Casella joins Matt to talk about his role as Dr. Marty Casey, the man who literally rips his own face off, scenes that didn't make the final cut of the film, and his relationship with Steven Spielberg and what led to Spielberg himself being the hands that ultimately rip his own face off. Plus, Matt celebrates the life of his wonderful grandmother Eleanor Gourley in a segment called I Was There Circa 1942.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85200</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198627</guid><pubDate>Wed, 03 Feb 2016 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198627.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3341</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[IWTT Classic:  Aliens | T2 | Titanic with Jenette Goldstein]]></title><description><![CDATA[From the vaults of I Was There Too, Matt brings out a classic episode with Jenette Goldstein of Aliens, T2, and Titanic. This week Jenette Goldstein joins Matt to chat about her portrayal as bad-ass Pvt. Vasquez in Aliens, John Connor’s foster mother in Terminator 2, and Irish Mommy in Titanic. Jenette tells us how she fell into the body building sub-culture in East London prior to being cast as Pvt. Vasquez, what it was like shooting in the huge vat of baby oil for the T-1000 in the lava bath scene, and using her own experience as a mother while putting her children to bed for the last time in Titanic. Plus, we finally lay some deep film score time signature controversy to rest as James Bladon returns in another edition of I Was There Tune.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85201</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198511</guid><pubDate>Tue, 05 Jan 2016 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198511.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4098</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Field of Dreams with Dwier Brown]]></title><description><![CDATA[Celebrate the one year anniversary of I Was There Too featuring Dwier Brown, aka Kevin Costner's dad, John Kinsella in 1989's Field of Dreams. Dwier tells us about how he prepared emotionally for his heartfelt father/son scene not long after his father had passed away, his book about the film entitled "If You Build It," Ray Liotta making his lucky Hawaiian shirt even more lucky on set, and much more. Plus, Matt's Superego buddy Mark McConville guides him through his first viewing of Field of Dreams in the debut of I Was There New.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85202</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198628</guid><pubDate>Wed, 11 Nov 2015 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198628.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3598</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Halloween with P.J. Soles]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress P.J. Soles joins Matt this week to talk about her role as Lynda van der Klok in the 1978 John Carpenter classic Halloween. P.J. talks about why the way she said "totally" secured her role in the film, what it's like to shoot a sex & death scene all at once, and her thoughts on her legendary death scene being recreated at Halloween Horror Nights at Universal Studios. P.J. also tells us her experience working with Bill Murray on Stripes, how she had to wrestle Rod Stewart for the jacket she would use for Rock 'n' Roll High School, and working alongside a very friendly Harrison Ford on the made for TV film The Possessed. Plus, filmmaker Jay Cheel of The Film Junk Podcast helps Matt face his Halloween fears on location during I Was Literally There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85203</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198629</guid><pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198629.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4055</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Total Recall with Ray Baker]]></title><description><![CDATA[Accomplished film and theatre actor Ray Baker joins Matt this week to talk about his many film/TV roles including helping Arnold Schwarzenegger go on his mind journey in Total Recall. Ray tells us about surviving Schwarzenegger's choke hold, playing a bad guy in a 21 Jump Street/Booker crossover episode, and working with Meryl Streep in Silkwood. Finally, James 'Jimmy Blades' Bladon joins Matt in another exciting installment of I Was There Tune to discuss the unveiling of their new theme song project called Stay Tuned vol. 1. A project that might even involve you! For more info on STAY TUNED vol. 1, visit this link: http://mattgourley.tumblr.com/tagged/stay-tuned-vol.-1   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85204</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198630</guid><pubDate>Wed, 14 Oct 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198630.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3419</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[I Wasn't There Too - Meet Dave with Paul Scheer]]></title><description><![CDATA[In a very special episode-long segment of I Wasnt There Too, actor, writer, and Wolfpops own Paul Scheer joins Matt to talk about his experience on the set of Meet Dave. Paul goes deep into how his role of Lieutenant Buttocks got re-cast during shooting, being fooled by Eddie Murphy doubles, and the wonderful rapport the real Eddie Murphy had with everyone on set. Plus, Paul tells us about one of his very first auditions for the Tom Cruise film Vanilla Sky.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85205</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198631</guid><pubDate>Wed, 30 Sep 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198631.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3138</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Waiting For Guffman | Best In Show | A Mighty Wind with Deborah Theaker]]></title><description><![CDATA[Phenomenal actress and improviser Deborah Theaker joins Matt this week to talk about her roles in a trilogy of Christopher Guest films. Deborah tells us about how George Lucas helped her get her green card, how bombing with the Kids in The Hall made her fearless onstage, making herself essential in Waiting For Guffman, and the real tears she shed in A Mighty Wind. Plus, Matt finally answers listener mail during I Was There Q&A!   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85206</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198632</guid><pubDate>Wed, 16 Sep 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198632.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2797</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mrs. Doubtfire with Lisa Jakub]]></title><description><![CDATA[Lisa Jakub began her acting career as a child in Canada and decided to retire from acting at the age of 22. Lisa joins Matt to talk about her many roles as a child actor including her role as Lydia Hillard in 1993s Mrs. Doubtfire. Lisa tells us about her experience improvising intimately with Robin Williams, her book You Look Like That Girl which chronicles her life as a child actress, and the one time she was almost kidnapped. Plus, Matt shares more children's cartoons that were based off R-rated movies in the debut of I Was R Too. RAMBO AND THE FORCES OF FREEDOM https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eliQEStzhu4 TOXIC CRUSADERS https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=mf2_g52p__Y TEENAGE MUTANT NINJA TURTLES https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=pOXS6f77Sek ROUGHNECKS: STARSHIP TROOPERS CHRONICLES https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l-97DMohl6o POLICE ACADEMY, THE SERIES https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YOE0F4i7GK8 OPERATION: ALIENS http://alienanthology.wikia.com/wiki/Operation:_Aliens BONUS: XENOMORPH COMMERCIAL https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=YQ8sYXVoAZA HIGHLANDER: THE ANIMATED SERIES https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=DRQHOc2gS-M ROBOCOP https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Yp4Sqn0eX_Q CONAN THE ADVENTURER https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6SsHfWBLVr0   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85207</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198633</guid><pubDate>Wed, 02 Sep 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198633.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2965</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Pulp Fiction with Phil LaMarr]]></title><description><![CDATA[Oh man, I shot Marvin in the face. These are the words John Travolta says after obliterating the face of this weeks guest, Phil LaMarr. Phil joins Matt to finally lay all the myths of Pulp Fiction to rest. Was Marvin originally supposed to survive? And whats Marvins real deal, anyway? And whats in the damned briefcase? Phil answers all of these questions as well as tells us about the real fear he felt in his scene with Samuel L. Jackson, the approach he takes when working on an impression, and his first job on the Mr. T cartoon while still attending high school. Plus, Matt shares which actors were in consideration to be in Pulp Fiction in the return of I Wasnt There Too! Check out the Rambo Cartoon Matt mentions in this ep here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=eliQEStzhu4   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85208</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198634</guid><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198634.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3054</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Clueless | Bring It On with Nicole Bilderback]]></title><description><![CDATA[As if! Wiggin Zup! Its been 20 years since Clueless hit theaters and changed the English language. This week actor, dancer, and martial artist Nicole Bilderback joins Matt to talk about her character Summer stealing a lit snowman, the story behind the Credit card Suck and Blow game, and the insane wardrobe budget for her character alone. Then, Nicole tells us about how the Mickey cheer/dance she prepared for her final Bring It On audition made its way into the film credits, her philanthropic organization, the New Hollywood, and being the unwitting poster girl for an IMDB lawsuit. Plus, Matt shares an example of how the vernacular of Clueless fits so seamlessly into any kind of dialogue during I Was There Clue-Less.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85209</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198635</guid><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198635.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2072</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Collected Stories Vol. 1: The Best Of I Was There Too]]></title><description><![CDATA[On a special episode of I Was There Too, Matt shares a compilation of some of the best stories from the last years guests. From the ups and downs of improvised lines with Paul F. Tompkins in There Will Be Blood, to whether Jenette Goldstein from Aliens thought her role was an immigrant alien or an extra-terrestrial alien, to tales of the infamous Schwabs Pharmacy with Matts grandmother Eleanor. Its worth revisiting if youre a regular listener and a perfect starting place for all the newbies. Plus, movie buffs Jeremy Smith, Devin Faraci, and Amy Nicholson put their film knowledge to the test in a game that incorporates the curious endings to the shows theme song, in the debut of I Quiz There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198636</guid><pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198636.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3528</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Friday the 13th with Derek Mears]]></title><description><![CDATA[Derek Mears portrayed one of the most famous slashers of all time, Jason Voorhees in the 2009 reboot of Friday the 13th. Derek joins Matt to talk about his action hero/cartoon character approach to the character, identifying with the young Tommy in Friday the 13th Part IV: The Final Chapter, and why the original ending of the film didnt test well with audiences. Derek also tells us about encountering a curious Harrison Ford while on the set of Indiana Jones and the Kingdom of the Crystal Skull, how he became a Classic Predator in Predators, and his experimental live improv action show The Resistance. Plus, Matt investigates which fictional character from cinema has killed the most people in a new segment called I Was Scared Too. The Resistance is a completely improvised action movie performed live on stage every Sunday night at 9pm at The Comedy Sportz Theater in Los Angeles. Go to https://www.facebook.com/resistancecmdy for more info! http://www.huffingtonpost.com/2012/10/31/jason-voorhees-kill-counter_n_2048684.html   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198637</guid><pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198637.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2696</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Deadwood with Paula Malcomson and Sarah Lund]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to Deadwood! Paula Malcomson joins Matt this week to talk about the evolving, unwritten arc of her character Trixie, her favorite phrase of curse, and the tenuous future life of the show. Then, Sarah Lund tells the story of how she went from a background actor to having a bathtub fitting for her big scene. It's a tale of two whores. One, a series regular and tough as nails. The other a featured background player and fancy as a June bride.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198513</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 06:17:18 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198513.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3459</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles with Josh Pais]]></title><description><![CDATA[Experience turtle power and celebrate the first and best Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles film with Raphael himself, actor Josh Pais. Josh talks about going from a kid who would get mugged all the time to a martial arts trained bad ass in East Village, New York City, becoming acclimated to the turtle suit, and fully committing to the emotional moment when Splinter is kidnapped. Josh also tells us about his training institution called Committed Impulse, playing Juniors lawyer in the Sopranos, and the upcoming biopic I Saw the Light. Plus, Matt shares an exclusive never before released Star Wars scene starring Margaux the Fat Guy as Padmé Naberrie in another edition of I Was There Mew.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198638</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198638.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2321</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[A Few Good Men with Joshua Malina]]></title><description><![CDATA[You cant handle truth. That actor Joshua Malina speaks this week as he joins Matt to chat about his role as Tom in A Few Good Men. Joshua talks about being in the original Broadway production of the same name before appearing in the film, saving Aaron Sorkins life, Clint Eastwood defending his manhood on the set of In the Line of Fire, and pranking his West Wing and Scandal castmates. Plus, Matt pits Bad News Bears against Dr. Strangelove in a battle for the best character names during I Was There Who? MALINA AND THE CAST OF THE WEST WING ON ELLEN: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=l5qgjAZIxYc MALINA ON KIMMEL: http://abc.go.com/shows/jimmy-kimmel-live/news/editors-picks/20141113-josh-malina-pranks-kerry-washington-and-the-cast-of-scandal   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520e</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198639</guid><pubDate>Wed, 27 May 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198639.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2967</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Léon: The Professional with Adam Busch]]></title><description><![CDATA[Wonderful actor and musician Adam Busch joins Matt to chat about how he went full method for his role as Manolo in Léon: The Professional. Adam talks about getting a full character background for Manolo directly from director Luc Besson, the charged sexual atmosphere on the set, Danny Aiello holding court on Ninth Avenue, and the alternate endings to the film which may or may not have included a musical number. Finally, Matt closes the show with a little taste of Eric Serra’s “The Experience of Love” which leads to an important exploration of the controversy behind some of the music of the James Bond franchise.NATALIE PORTMAN’S AUDITION: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JhRW8J3gTuoGARY OLDMAN ACTING PILLS: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=74BzSTQCl_cGARY OLDMAN ‘BRING ME EVERYONE!’: https://youtu.be/d7G9qi9MYhc   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8520f</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198640</guid><pubDate>Tue, 12 May 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198640.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2742</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Better Off Dead with Diane Franklin]]></title><description><![CDATA[Magnifique! Diane Franklin, the princess of 80s movies, joins Matt to chat about her role as the French foreign exchange student Monique Junet in Better Off Dead. Diane talks about her character being an ace baseball pitcher, expert skier, and overall bad-ass, why you should have to be able to act without words, the controversy surrounding John Cusack being upset after watching Better Off Dead for the first time, and more. Diane also tells us about her cut prom scene in Bill and Teds Excellent Adventure, her book Diane Franklin: The Excellent Adventures of the Last American, French-Exchange Babe of the 80s, and her idea for a Babes of the 80s party. Plus, Matt has a special assignment for all of you Siri users in a new segment called I am Always There Too! Todays sponsor is Casper Mattresses - obsessively engineered American-made mattresses at a shockingly fair price. And now, you can get $50 toward any mattress purchase by going to casper.com/iwtt and using code iwtt!   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85210</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198641</guid><pubDate>Wed, 29 Apr 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198641.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3206</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Groundhog Day with Stephen Tobolowsky]]></title><description><![CDATA[Bing! Actor extraordinaire Stephen Tobolowsky joins Matt to chat about his role as Ned Ryerson, the insurance salesman who pesters Bill Murray each and every morning in Groundhog Day. Stephen talks about shooting his famous scene in every weather condition imaginable, improvising with Bill Murray, Harold Ramis as a personal hero, and much more. Stephen also tells us about his experience on Deadwood, working with a spiritually-transformed Steven Seagal, and the worst squibbing of his life. Plus, Matt interviews a very special lady in his life in a new segment called I Was There Mew. This episode is sponsored by Draftkings. Hurry to Draft Kings.com NOW and use promo code DRAFT5 to play for free in the hundred thousand dollar fantasy baseball contest on Opening Day! First place takes home ten thousand dollars.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85211</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198642</guid><pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198642.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3397</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Captain America: The Winter Soldier with D.C. Pierson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Writer and comedian D.C. Pierson joins Matt to chat about his role as Aaron, the Apple store employee who helps and potentially hinders Captain America and Black Widow on their rogue quest for information in Captain America: The Winter Soldier. Their conversation on D.C.s 26 second scene of screen time covers the surprisingly good feeling you get on a trip to the Apple store, comics, their specific feelings on the Target stores in their neighborhood, and more. Plus, Matt shares a teaser from Paul F. Tompkins exciting new podcast Spontaneanation which is available now on Earwolf. This episode is sponsored by Draftkings. Hurry to Draft Kings.com NOW and use promo code DRAFT5 to play for free in the hundred thousand dollar fantasy baseball contest on Opening Day! First place takes home ten thousand dollars.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85212</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198643</guid><pubDate>Thu, 02 Apr 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198643.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3525</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aliens | T2 | Titanic with Jenette Goldstein]]></title><description><![CDATA[This week Jenette Goldstein joins Matt to chat about her portrayal as bad-ass Pvt. Vasquez in Aliens, John Connors foster mother in Terminator 2, and Irish Mommy in Titanic. Jenette tells us how she fell into the body building sub-culture in East London prior to being cast as Pvt. Vasquez, what it was like shooting in the huge vat of baby oil for the T-1000 in the lava bath scene, and using her own experience as a mother while putting her children to bed for the last time in Titanic. Plus, we finally lay some deep film score time signature controversy to rest as James Bladon returns in another edition of I Was There Tune. This episode is sponsored by: Hullo. Go to hullopillow.com/IWTT and order today. You can save $5, $10, or $20 on each additional pillow you purchase depending on size! Harry's. Go to Harrys.com now and Harrys will give you $5 off if you type in IWTT at checkout with your first purchase.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85213</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200203533</guid><pubDate>Tue, 24 Mar 2015 17:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200203533.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3721</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Exorcist with Eileen Dietz]]></title><description><![CDATA[Things get spooky this week as Eileen Dietz, the face of the demon Pazuzu aka Captain Howdy joins Matt to chat about being in the most famous horror movie of all time, The Exorcist. Eileen tells us the differences between the roles of Pazuzu & Captain Howdy, channeling wild animals for her improvised audition, her process with all the prosthetics, particularly with the puking apparatus, and her book Exorcising My Demons. Plus, Matt talks about the actors, directors, and composers who were considered to be a part of the film in a Variety Pack edition of I Wasnt There Too. Enjoy hearing what it was like to puke pea green soup on a sub arctic set with a director slapping people and firing guns into the air.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85214</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198644</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2015 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198644.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2764</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Inglourious Basterds with Paul Rust]]></title><description><![CDATA[Prepare to be transported back to World War II as Paul Rust talks to Matt about his role as Private First Class Andy Kagan in Quentin Tarantinos Inglourious Basterds. Paul tells us about nerding out over movies with Tarantino the first time they met, having to take a 101 course in scalping, and a special gift he received from Brad Pitt. Plus, Matt goes through the names of other actors who were in talks to appear in the film in another edition of I Wasnt There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85215</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198645</guid><pubDate>Wed, 18 Feb 2015 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198645.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3377</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Goodfellas with Johnny Williams]]></title><description><![CDATA[Get yourself a good meatball hero sandwich or a bowl of pasta as you listen to Johnny Williams talk to Matt about his role as Johnny Roastbeef in Martin Scorseses Goodfellas. Well hear about the origin of the name Johnny Roastbeef, Johnnys early beginnings of owning a deli in East Harlem, meeting Scorsese & De Niro, busting balls with Joe Pesci, and his death scene which leads off one of the greatest montages in film history. Plus, Matt shares some actual fun facts about the real characters and events in Goodfellas during I Was Really There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85216</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198646</guid><pubDate>Wed, 04 Feb 2015 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198646.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2657</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Speed with the Passengers of Bus 2525]]></title><description><![CDATA[Pop quiz, hotshot. What has a bus, a bomb, and five fascinating interview subjects? The I Was There Too Speed Super-sode. Simone Gad, David Kriegel, Carmen Williams, Hawthorne James, and Carlos Carrasco join Matt to talk about their fateful ride on bus 2525 from the 1994 action classic. Take your seat and tilt dat booty.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85217</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198515</guid><pubDate>Wed, 21 Jan 2015 09:03:46 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198515.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>4813</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Captain EO with Doug Benson]]></title><description><![CDATA[Happy 2015 everyone! Doug Benson is known as a lover of movies and he joined Matt this week to discuss how his love of movies lead him to be an orange dancer in the Disney multidimensional attraction Captain EO. Doug tells us about his time working as a PA for Michael Jackson, watching MJ do his signature moonwalk on the set, how Dougs views on MJ which he shared on Doug Loves Movies where badly timed, and being squibbed in Return of the Living Dead II. Plus, Matt welcomes his grandmother Eleanor Gourley to talk about falling in love with Cesar Romero and much more when she lived near the infamous Schwabs Pharmacy and Garden of Allah Hotel in a segment called I Was There Circa 1942.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85218</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198647</guid><pubDate>Sat, 17 Jan 2015 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198647.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3388</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Caddyshack with Peter Berkrot]]></title><description><![CDATA[Gather round the ol fireplace this Christmas Eve and listen to actor Peter Berkrot as he joins Matt virtually from Gloucester, Massachusetts this week to discuss his role as Angie DAnnunzio in Caddyshack. Peter tells us about how Tom Hulce got him the audition for the movie, how the infamous Bill Murray pitchfork Dalai Lama scene took 7 hours to shoot, and how through luck & editing, his role became a much larger one. Plus, Matt introduces a new segment called The King and I Was There Too, where he is joined by his old chum/Whose Line Is It Anyway regular Jeff B. Davis to talk about playing Louis in the King and I on tour & on Broadway. Check out a young Jeff Davis in a Madballs commercial and on Highway to Heaven below! https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yvfYcZ8GAVM https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=JOgthVkU8JY   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d85219</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198648</guid><pubDate>Wed, 24 Dec 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198648.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3139</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[The Untouchables with Melody Rae]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actress Melody Rae joins Matt via phone from Yelm, Washington this week to discuss her role as the woman with the baby carriage in the Union Station staircase shoot out in The Untouchables. Melody tells us about completely improvising her memorable scene, how she handled the explosions, baby, & squibs, and working with Kevin Costner. Plus, Matt introduces a new segment called I Was There Tune, where he is joined by his good friend/music editor/composer James Jimmy Blades Bladon to talk about composing music, working with director Tony Scott, sound effects, and life behind the mixer. Finally, Matt closes out the show by talking about how Mickey Rourke was originally going to play Eliot Ness in another installment of I Wasnt There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8521a</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198649</guid><pubDate>Wed, 10 Dec 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198649.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2798</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace with Greg Proops]]></title><description><![CDATA[The smartest man in the world, Greg Proops joins Matt this week to discuss his role as Fode in Star Wars Episode I: The Phantom Menace. Greg shares how he was cast alongside Scott Capurro while performing stand-up in Edinburgh around 1997, what it was like meeting George Lucas for the first time while wearing a blue latex outfit & full character makeup, and his reaction when he found out he was turned into a completely CGI character. Plus, Matt brings up the rumor of Benicio Del Toro originally playing Darth Maul in another exciting installment of I Wasnt There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8521b</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198650</guid><pubDate>Wed, 26 Nov 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198650.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>3120</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[Aliens with Ricco Ross]]></title><description><![CDATA[Actor and writer Ricco Ross joins Matt this week to discuss his role as Private Frost in the film Aliens. Ricco explains what Arcturian Poontang is and what it means to hammer some of that down, takes us through his difficult decision of turning down a role in a Stanley Kubrick film for Aliens, shares the story behind the white heart with the name Heath on his characters chest plate, and talks about what it was like working with James Cameron & Sigourney Weaver. Plus, Matt sheds some more light on why James Remar was replaced by Michael Biehn as the male lead in the film another installment of I Wasnt There Too. Check out Ricco Ross ALS/PIC project here: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=6dJr-eH7cwY   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8521c</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198651</guid><pubDate>Wed, 12 Nov 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198651.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season/><itunes:duration>2524</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item><item><title><![CDATA[There Will Be Blood with Paul F. Tompkins]]></title><description><![CDATA[Welcome to the first episode of I Was There Too with Matt Gourley. The show where Matt will talk to people who were present in the great scenes of cinema history. Mayor of podcasts Paul F. Tompkins joins Matt to discuss his role as Mr. Prescott in the film There Will Be Blood. Paul tells us how he got to know Paul Thomas Anderson through the Largo comedy scene and about the strange noises Daniel Day-Lewis makes in between takes. Plus, Matt talks about the people who were originally cast in There Will Be Blood in a segment called I Wasnt There Too.   Hosted on Acast. See acast.com/privacy for more information.]]></description><link>https://shows.acast.com/i-was-there-too/episodes/633da86c23a2950012d8521d</link><guid isPermaLink="false">Unofficial-RSS-v2-200198652</guid><pubDate>Mon, 03 Nov 2014 16:00:00 GMT</pubDate><enclosure url="S3_BUCKET_URL/1001575/200198652.mp3" length="1" type="audio/mpeg"/><itunes:episodeType>full</itunes:episodeType><itunes:season>1</itunes:season><itunes:duration>2935</itunes:duration><googleplay:explicit>true</googleplay:explicit><itunes:explicit>true</itunes:explicit></item></channel></rss>